bnp.org.uk 2010-11-20

# Privacy Policy | British National Party

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

_(1) What information do we collect?_

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:

(a) Information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website including your IP address, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views.

(b) Information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services.

(c) Information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us including email address.

(d) Information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters.

(e) Any other information that you choose to send to us.

_(2) Cookies_

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We use “persistent” cookies on the website. We will use the persistent cookies to enable our website to remember your login details when you visit.

Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.

_  (3) Using your personal data_

Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use your personal information to:

(a) Administer the website.

(b) Improve your browsing experience by personalising the website.

(c) Enable your use of the services available on the website.

(d) Send to you goods purchased via the website, and supply to you services purchased via the website.

(e) Send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you.

(f) Send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications.

(g) Send you email notifications which you have specifically requested.

(h) Send to you marketing communications which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications).

(i) Deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website.

Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us.

We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.

_(4) Disclosures_

We may disclose information about you to our employees, officers or agents insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.

In addition, we may disclose information about you:

(a) To the extent that we are required to do so by law;

(b) In connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;

(c) In order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk).

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

_(5) Security of your personal data_

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password – and firewall – protected) servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted using SSL technology.

Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password.

_(6) Policy amendments_

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.

_(7) Your rights_

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you.

You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email at any time. In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes.

_(8) Third party websites_

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

_(9) Updating information_

Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

_(10) Contact_

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to webmaster@bnp.org.uk
